Olivia Ovalle /

Associate

Practice Area: Insurance Law

olivia.ovalle@ocl.cl

Olivia has focused on insurance law and is counsel to insurance companies. She has ample experience in insurance tenders, the negotiation of policy renewals, legal risk audits and insurance programs as well as out-of-court loss settlements. She has been counsel to different clients regarding an integral administration of their insurance policies and the drafting of insurance clauses.

WORK HISTORY

2015 - present / Ovalle Consejeros Legales

2014 - 2015 / Estudio Zárate y Associates

2014 - 2015 / La Calera Civil Court

EDUCATION

Diploma in Insurance Law, Concentration in General Insurance: Marine Damages and Marine Insurance, Pontifical Catholic University of Chile, 2016 B.A. in Legal and Social Sciences, minor in Social Communication, Adolfo Ibáñez University. Admissions: 2014

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE

- Aid in the Obligations Course, Adolfo Ibáñez University.
- Aid in the Civil Liability Course, Adolfo Ibáñez University.
- Aid in the Family Law Course, Adolfo Ibáñez University.

LANGUAGES

Spanish, English and German

LINKEDIN

www.linkedin.com/in/olivia-ovalle-duclos-973365b8